Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Round two, match one of the Royal Knight's selection exam.
Soul trapped Mimosa with her magic.
Asta defended their crystal from Magna, who launched an all-out solo attack. Then...
Seems you're forgetting about this, dashing mage.
Yikes, two against one. Not good.
Asta's mysterious teammate, Zerx, came to his rescue.
Go after the flower guy! Do it now!
This will only slow me for a moment, that's all I need! To beat you!
Mimosa deployed a plant spell that stopped Soul's Golem in its tracks.
And Asta and the rest of Team B were able to claim victory.
And now, Finral and Longris prepare to face off.
Who will win in this Battle of Brothers?
Mimosa.
Kikiiki, kimi no koto.
Wah wah wah wah, wa wa kara na i da kara.
Wah wah wah, boku no koto.
Kikiiki, kiko maata shira na i de sho.
Wah wah wah, wok mo koto.
Wah wah wah, wakaru to kata ni iwa nai.
Give me theusion.
I'll give you Fürig.
My centrally surrounded by GEGA .
Rune a little Avec ок guer,
Is it just a glove-ruck with nasseku?
Oh.
Now over that each side fell apart,
Thank you!
他的富貴
That's much better.
Uh, thank-you, Vanessa. That's great.
Great? Try perfect!
You look awesome, Finral!
Yeah, you think you could do mine next?
Why would I style a loser's hair?
You look fine to me, like the failure that you are.
Oh, yeah? Come over here and say that!
Hey, take it easy, Magnet. Just try to stay calm, like a loser should.
Hey! You mess with me right now, and I'm gonna kill you!
Sounds like someone's looking to spar!
Whoa, whoa! It's not the time!
In spite of his rough looks, that guy seems like he knows his way around flame magic.
The lightning mage is skilled as well.
Hey there! You got any more food, mister?
My goodness, for something your size, you certainly can't eat!
Marie, Angel, how I miss you, my darling.
What's going on?
It's just the black bulls.
Still the same idiots they've always been.
Stop! This is embarrassing! You're making all of us look bad!
You're looking a little stiff there.
Worried, huh?
About the match? And who you're facing?
Well, yeah, a little.
I mean, he might be my younger brother, but I've never beaten him at anything.
Don't worry. I've fought alongside you, so I know. You changed after meeting Asta, just like I did. Thanks to him, I was finally able to face something I'd hidden deep inside my heart.
You're not going to lose to him so easily anymore. Go show him how awesome you are. And I don't just mean the hair.
Thanks, Vanessa.
She's right! You totally got this!
I want to fight you, so don't be a big loser like Magna!
Yeah, don't be a big loser like Magna!
That's it! I'm going to kill you!
We'll all be rooting for you, Cinderella!
You can do it. You can do it. You can do it.
You'd better not blow this match and embarrass the rest of the squad.
Wow. You guys, thank you all. I don't know what to say. I'm so happy I joined the Black Bulls. You're like a family.
Feed me, feed me, feed me, feed me, feed me, feed me, feed me, feed me!
Hurry up and win this. I need to return to Marie as soon as possible.
I'm your superior!
And I'm sure Captain Yami's cheering you on back at the hideout, too.
That's right. His stomach wasn't feeling well, or else I'd know he would have been here to show his support.
Even so, I'm sure he wants you to work hard. With or without him.
Huh. Those morons are probably pushing past their limits right now.
Just like I'm about to. This is the biggest dump the world's ever seen.
Dammit, kid! I told you to restock the toilet paper!
Give up now. You must know you stand no chance of defeating me.
No, you're wrong. Thanks to my friends, I'm stronger than I used to be. Our team will win.
We'll see about that, brother. Don't blame me if you get hurt.
If it's okay with you, I'd like to handle him myself.
Hmm. Seems fine.
A battle between brothers. I hope to test my fighting prowess against my own brother someday.
So, yes, I agree to your request and wish you the best of luck.
Ha ha! I'll ride this Seke shooting star to victory.
All shall remember my performance.
Your team won't lay a finger on our crystal in this match.
Ah! It's finally starting!
I can't help but feel nervous for him.
You can win this, Finral. I know you can.
And now, Team E, comprised of Leopold, Hammond, and Finral, versus Langris, Fragile, and Seke of Team G.
Round two, match two, begin!
You guys concentrate on destroying their crystal.
We've got this.
First, we need to determine its location.
Now, glass magic fair detection!
The light will reflect off the glass shards scattered throughout the battleground, and every last inch of it will be revealed to me.
This may take some time, but rest assured, I've no doubt I will find the enemy's crystal.
Oh.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I expect you to take me all the way to the enemy base again, Mr. Ha ha ha.
Leave it to me! And the name's actually Seke?
Please feel free to use it.
You can even call me Sec for short. Ha ha!
Whatever you say, Mr. Ha ha.
Ha ha! No, I just told you!
It's Seke! Seke!
Seke!
You brought shame upon the House of Fod.
There's no way I'll let you defeat me today.
How could I possibly love you?
You aren't even my own flesh and blood.
My sweet little Longris is the only child I need.
Come now, Mother, don't you think it's a bit cruel to put it so bluntly?
What can you accomplish with that?
Learn to attack like Longris!
What do you know?
My Longris is both more athletic and more intelligent than you.
Ha ha ha ha!
You're so amazing, darling Longris.
Yes, as I should expect from my own flesh and blood.
Unlike you, Findle, you're a disgrace to the Fod name.
How pathetic.
He's the older brother, but there's not a single thing he can do better than me.
What? A fiancé?
Yes. This is Lady Finnis. She will marry the next head of the House of Vord.
Nice to meet you.
Her chronic illness keeps her housebound mostly, but the king is her great-uncle, so she comes from a prestigious family, and her magic is impressive.
Ugh. This is the woman I'm going to marry? Couldn't father have chosen someone less... dull?
Now remember, dear, Lady Finnis is going to be your bride someday, so you must try to get along with her.
Of course!
Honestly, I don't need a wife with a fancy title. When I'm the lord of this house, I'll bring more honor to the Vod family than anyone has before.
Ugh. I'm so bored.
I'm very sorry. I doubt many men would choose to marry a woman who's both sickly and older than they are.
I... I mean, any man would be lucky to have a wife as beautiful as you, Lady Finnis.
It's just that I'm not actually the one who will become the next head of House of Vod.
I'm sure my younger brother will make you happy, though. He's better at everything than I am.
His magic's amazing, and he's really brave. Compared to him, I'm a total failure.
Exactly. At least he realizes he's inferior to me and...
No, you're wrong. I know I've only met you a few times, but I can tell. You're a very kind, considerate person.
So if you ask me, you're a better mage than your brother will ever be.
Oh! You're joking, of course! Please don't tease me like that!
Don't be silly. I wasn't teasing you at all.
Who does the sparrow think she is? Rating me lower than that failure.
Utterly absurd. He left the family because he couldn't handle the pressure.
He's not better than me at anything. Not a single thing!
Ha-ha! We found it!
Well, I hope you're ready, Finral, because here he comes.
Remember what I said. Don't blame me if you wind up losing a limb or two.
I'll end this in a single blow!
What?
That's right. I tested this earlier with Cobb.
Something happens when spatial magic spells clash.
The monocurrents within them collide, causing them to cancel each other out.
Just like that!
Longris, you won't win this time!
That's so cool!
So two spatial magic spells cancel each other out?
He didn't see that coming.
It's like Finral's a totally different person out there!
Lose at this point and I'll kill ya!
Hurry up and finish it. Marie's waiting.
I can almost taste the Victory Cupcakes now!
Uh, huh?
Ha-ha-ha!
It looks like we made a good choice letting you take him on.
Hammond! Any luck yet?
Yes! I finally found the enemy's crystal!
It's hidden within that tower!
Right! Now go!
Quickly!
They're gone!
You've gotten too cocky, but I'll put you back in your place!
Step aside! We're gonna destroy that crystal!
We'll see about that.
What's this?
Snow magic. Phantom Snow Garden.
Do you feel it yet?
This spell both deadens your senses and induces sleep.
While it's active, you won't be able to attack me effectively.
Uh...
Yeah, right!
I'm not tired at all!
This is nothing compared to my older sister's training!
Nothing!
Did you honestly think that this would be enough?
Exactly!
We can take her, no problem!
I could eat five more helpings.
Still have room left.
You're talking in your sleep?
Why fight it? You look like you can use the rest.
Those flames!
I bear the house vermilion symbol of an oath made to oneself!
I swore a vow that one day I would surpass my brother!
So I'm not about to lose to somebody like you!
There's no way!
Monastin!
Go, flame magic!
Spiral flame!
His senses are still sharp.
He managed to nullify my spell by enveloping himself in mana.
Stay strong!
Can't lose my concentration!
I won't last much longer.
Hurry, Longris.
Ah!
A battle between two adept spatial magic users!
You don't see one of those every day!
Oh!
So that's the vaude boy Venus is going to marry.
He's talented.
Still no match for me, though.
Keep it up, Fenril!
You've got him now!
You just have to hold out until the other two destroy the enemy's crystal!
Who knew?
I never imagined you had what it took to stand against me.
Do you plan on playing defense all by yourself until your crystal breaks?
I'm not going to make it easy!
I'm sure you won't.
That's fine.
Because I came prepared to fight!
Ha ha!
You're an even bigger idiot than I realized if you think a sluggish spell like that could ever catch my marvelous self!
Incoming?
That's an interesting feature, but it's still no match for my invincible Seke Magnum Cannonball!
Ha ha ha!
What?
He just disappeared?
Even I think it's pitiful.
I trained like crazy, but it didn't matter.
I never managed to learn a single attack spell.
Wait.
It's not an attack spell?
That's spatial magic.
Fallen Angel's wingbeat.
It follows the enemy, makes contact, then transports them to another location.
It's a battlefield application of the spell I usually use.
He adapted a basic spatial magic spell so he can get rid of his enemies without harming them!
Clearly, this is a mage who possesses a truly gentle soul!
I knew you could do more than just flirt with girls!
He's gone.
I wonder where the portal took him, though.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I was this close to pinchin' it off.
You're dead meat.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Longris, it's only a matter of time before my teammates destroy your crystal.
I don't want to hurt my own brother.
Give up, or you'll disappear too.
you're worried about hurting me you're as annoying as you are incompetent
who would have thought our special reserve spells would be so similar
how dare you force me to use my grimoire's magic
there isn't a single thing you can beat me at and there never will be
this threatening feeling i recognize it wait i know this mana
what happened my goodness i must say this is quite unpleasant
as i suspected it's over brother his magic i already knew i didn't stand a chance against a
mage as strong as my brother but something else is going on here something strange
i've felt magic like this before
who are you get out of there if that attack hits him run then roll
no he's longer he's my little brother you may not like it but we're similar so what if we come from
different mothers i never acted like an older sibling should i left our family and tried to forget
everything
but i couldn't
no matter what you think no matter what we've been through
you're still my little brother
please lagris stop this right now for i don't know how much longer you'll stay
you give me a break what could you possibly understand about me you ran abandoned your house
you're a coward who can't even attack somebody in battle you're nothing
i'll stop you
you can never beat me
such different boys young master finral's so kind and very popular too unlike his little brother
you can tell that boy looks down on everybody he talks to such a shame
well if you ask me you're a much better mage she seems so kind but even she hates me
longress you can take one day off of studying can't you come goof off with your big brother
i'll be at the festival if you want to join me why is he so nice to me stop it be more like
longress my longress is so amazing i'm better than he is that's why mother and father are always kind
so nice to me i have to beat him at everything everything otherwise i'll i'll
see that he's going after the guy on the ground why the match is over
disappear
you
benrael he won't last long with wounds like these
hey go on take one more step toward him but you should know that the second you do you're dead
this bastard you're going to pay for this i can't believe he would do that
monster
there's something wrong with you the match was already over
me
i'm
Thank you.
That new spell was totally awesome! Fallen Angel's weightlifting!
That was close, but not quite.
Well, sometimes you gotta shake things up, you know?
That's the only way to get stronger.
Oh, yeah?
So, are you gonna get a new hairdo every time you need to beef up your magic?
That could be cool.
Uh, I don't know.
You should try one of those pompadour things next.
Or maybe Captain Yami's hairstyle.
Or a yummy soft serve swirl.
That looks like poop.
This one looks pretty tough.
If you try Marie's hairstyle, I'll kill you.
Or, um, maybe something like this?
Well, personally, I think this one would be more attractive.
For no particular reason, of course.
Come on, you need something like that.
I'm mature.
This one here is for pushing past your limits!
No, seriously!
My life would be complete if I could only see this hairstyle on you, Vidro!
I've got more to worry about right now than my hair!
Praise me as I deserve, for I am your benevolent and mighty sovereign!
Next time on Black Clover, page 81, The Life of a Certain Man.
I said praise me!